Inventory of the Great Britain, Foreign Office, Wellington House publications
Hoover Institution Archives
- Van der Linden, Herman and Hamelius, Paul. "Anglo-Belgian Relations, Past and Present." Constable, London, 1918, 117 pp. (Box 11)
- Van Houtte, Paul. "The Pan-Germanic Crime". Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1915, 192 p. (Box 16)
- "The Violation of the Neutrality of Belgium." Darling, London, 1915, 22 pp. (Box 11)
- Visscher, Ch. de. "Belgium's Case. A Judicial Enquiry." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1916, 164 p. (Box 16)
- Wallenstrein, Abraham. "Jews and Germanism." and "Jewish Chronicle", London, 1918, 14 pp. (Box 12)
- "The War and the German Propaganda. A Swiss View of Germany's Aims." Eyre and Spottiswoode, London, 1915, 12 pp. (Box 12)
- "War for Ever." The Beacon, No. 3. Leaflet. R. Clay & Son, London. (Box 12)
- "A War of Liberation." Reprinted from the Round Table, for June, 1917, Macmillan, London, 37 pp. (Box 12)
- "The War on Hospital Ships. With Narratives of Eye-Witnesses and British and German Diplomatic Correspondence." Second & Revised Edition. T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1918, 40 pp. (Box 12)
- "The War, Prospect and Retrospect. Report of Speeches Delivered by the Rt. Hon. Winston Churchill, M. P., First Lord of the Admiralty, (House of Commons, Nov. 27, 1914) Field Marshal the Rt. Hon. Earl Kitcherner, Secretary of State for War, (House of Lords, 26 November, 1914 and The Rt. Hon David Lloyd George, M. P., Chancellor of the Exchequer.) House of Commons, 27th November, 1914." 23 pp. (Box 12)
- Ward, Humphry (Mrs.). "Toward the Goal." John Murray, London, 1917. 246 p. (Box 16)
- Ward, Wilfrid. "England and the War." Eyre & Spottiswoode, London, 1914. 18 pp. (Box 12)
- Warren, Herbert, (Sir). A. C. Benson, Sir Alfred Pearce Gould, et al. "British Universities and the War. A Record and Its Meaning." Field & Queen, London, 1917, 98 pp. (Box 12)
- "We See with Regret the Name of Many German Professors and Men of Science... (first line)." Horace Hart, Oxford, 8 pp. (Box 12)
- Wedgewood, Josiah. "With Machine-Guns in Gallipoli." Reprinted from the Westminster Gazette. Darling, London, 1915, 22 pp. (Box 12)
- Weizmann, Chaim. and Richard Gottheil. "What is Zionism? Two Chapters from Zionism and the Jewish Future." Zionist Organization, London, 1918, 44 pp. (Box 12)
- Weston, Frank. "The Black Slaves of Prussia. An Open Letter Addressed to General Smuts," Universities' Mission to Central Africa, London, 16 pp. (Box 12)
- "Where the German Army Has Passed." Illustrated with 53 Special Photographs. Daily Chronicle, London, 1915, 66 pp. (Box 12)
- Whitlock, Brand. "The Deportations. Statement by the American Minister to Belgium." T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1917, 8 pp. (Box 12)
- Wiart, Carton de. "The Way of Honour." George Allen & Unwin, London, 1918, 256 p. (Box 16)
- Wile, Frederic William. "Explaining the Britishers." Heinmann, London, 1918. 118 p. (Box 12)
- Williams, J. E. Hodder. "One Young Man. True Story of a Clerk who Enlisted in 1914, Fought for Nearly Two Years, Was Severely Wounded at the Battle of the Somme, and Is Now on His Way Back to His Desk." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 174. (Box 16)
- Williamson, David. "Lloyd-George, A Man of the People." Doran, New York, 1917, 36 pp. (Box 12)
- Wilson, Woodrow. "The Challenge Accepted. President Wilson's Address to Congress April 2d, 1917." T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1917, 8 pp. (Box 12)
- "The Work and Training of the Royal Flying Corps." Illustrated London News, London. 46 pp. (Box 12)
- "The Work and Training of the Royal Naval Air Service." Illustrated London News, London, 46 pp. (Box 12)
- "The Work and Training of the Royal Naval Naval Reserve." Yachting Monthly, London, 64 pp. (Box 12)
- "The World's Largest Loan." T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1917, 8 pp. (Box 12)
- "Wounded and a Prisoner of War. By an Exchange Officer." Blackwood, London, 1916, 316 pp. (Box 16)
- Yates, L. K. "The Woman's Part. A Record of Munitions Work." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1918, 64 pp. 24 plates. (Box 12)
- Zimmermann, Emil. "The German Empire of Central Africa." Longmans, Green & Co. London, 1918, 63 pp. (Box 12)
- Zimmern, A. E. "The Economic Weapon in the War Against Germany." George Alle and Unwin, London, 1918, 20 pp. (Box 12)
- Cardfile index of titles (Box 18)
  Cardfile duplicates this title list.